A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Two young women on horseback, with a man standing close by.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0224; 4x5
- Two young women on horseback, with a man standing nearby.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0225; 4x5
- Two young women and a young men on horseback, with a man attaching ribbons to their horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0226; 4x5
- Side view of a young woman on horseback, a ribbon on the horse’s head.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0227; 4x5
- Front diagonal view of a young woman on horseback, a ribbon on the horse’s head.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0228; 4x5
- A young woman posing on her horse, with the rear end of another horse in the foreground.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0229; 4x5
- A young woman posing horseback, a ribbon on her horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0230; 4x5
- A young woman posing horseback, a ribbon on her horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0231; 4x5
- Two young women and young man on horseback, with another man attaching ribbons to their horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0232; 4x5
- Side view of a young woman posing on horseback. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0233; 4x5
- Side view of a young woman posing on horseback, a ribbon on her horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0234; 4x5
- Side view of a woman approaching a horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0235; 4x5
- Side view of a woman on horseback, conversing with a man that is standing in the foreground.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0236; 4x5
- Front diagonal view of a man on horseback, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0237; 4x5
- A man and a woman riding on two separate horses, with another man attaching ribbons to each horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0238; 4x5
- Side view of a man on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the side of his horse’s head.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0239; 4x5
- Two young women and a young man riding on horseback, with another man attaching ribbons to their horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0240; 4x5
- Side view of a woman standing face to face with a horse, its reins in her hands.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0241; 4x5
- Side view of a man on horseback, with another man attaching a ribbon to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0242; 4x5
- Two young women riding separate horses, with a man standing close by. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0243; 2.5x3.5
- A young woman on horseback, a ribbon on the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0244; 2.5x3.5
- Two young women riding on horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0245; 2.5x3.5
- A woman on horseback, with a man standing next to her.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0246; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a woman standing face to face with a horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0247; 2.5x3.5
- Man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0248; 4x5
- Side view of a man on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0249; 4x5
  Negative is very faded.
- Side view of a man on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0250; 4x5
- Two men riding two separate horses, with another man approaching one of the horses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0251; 4x5
- A man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0252; 4x5
- Side view of a man riding a horse, with a ribbon attached to the horse’s bridle.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0253; 4x5
- A young woman on horseback, with a man attaching a ribbon to her horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0254; 4x5
- A man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0255; 4x5
- View of a man riding horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0256; 4x5
- A man riding a horse that has a ribbon attached to its bridle.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0257; 4x5
- Front view of a man on a horse and another man standing next to him.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0258; 4x5
- Side view of two men riding separate horses and facing each other.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0259; 4x5
- A man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0260; 4x5
- Side view of a horse with a ribbon attached to its bridle, and a man standing close by.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0261; 4x5
- Front view of two men on horseback.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0262; 4x5
- A man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0263; 4x5
- A man riding a horse with a ribbon attached to its bridle, and another man standing in the foreground with his back to the camera.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0264; 4x5
- Front view of a man riding on horseback and conversing with a man that is standing next to him.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0265; 2.5x3.5
- Man posing on horseback, with a ribbon attached to the horse.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0266; 2.5x3.5
- A man riding on horseback, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0267; 2.5x3.5
- A young woman facing a horse and holding its reins.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0268; 2.5x3.5
- A man riding on horseback and holding a lance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0269; 4x5
- A man riding on horseback.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0270; 4x5
- A man riding on horseback and carrying a lance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0271; 4x5
- A group of four men and three women, a few of whom holding lances.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0272; 4x5
- A man jousting, with spectators on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0273; 4x5
- A man riding on horseback and carrying a lance, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0274; 4x5
- A man jousting with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0275; 4x5
- A man riding on horseback, with spectators on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0276; 4x5
- A man jousting with spectators on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0277; 4x5
- A man jousting with spectators on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0278; 4x5
- Side view of a man on horseback holding a lance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0279; 4x5
- A variety of horse riders and spectators.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0280; 2.5x3.5
- “John Deere Day,” crowds of people outside of the John Deere Farm Equipment store.1947, Image: P0002.03.0281; 4x5
  Series 8a, “Other Events and Entertainment: John Deere Day,” begins.
- “John Deere Day,” large crowds of people outside of the John Deere Farm Equipment store. 1947, Image: P0002.03.0282; 4x5
- “John Deere Day,” a number of women standing behind a long table of refreshments.1947, Image: P0002.03.0283; 4x5
- “John Deere Day,” farm equipment on display outside of the John Deere store.1947, Image: P0002.03.0284; 2.5x3.5
- “John Deere Day,” a small boy sitting in front of a large tractor tire display.1947, Image: P0002.03.0285; 4x5
- “John Deere Day,” a woman driving a John Deere tractor.1947, Image: P0002.03.0286; 2.5x3.5
- “John Deere Day,” close-up view of a young boy sitting on or driving a John Deere tractor.1947, Image: P0002.03.0287; 2.5x3.5
- A large group of men wearing suits posing at a banquet of sorts hosted by the Gulf company.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0288; 4x5
  Series 8b, “Other Events and Entertainment: Gulf Banquet,” begins.
- Duplicate of P0002.03.0288.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0288a; 4x5
- Three men in suits conversing at the head of the table at a banquet hosted by the Gulf company.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0289; 4x5
- A man presenting another man with a plaque at the head of the table at a banquet hosted by the Gulf company. Plaque reads “To Joseph Rhodes in recognition and appreciation of our business association which began in 1933.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0290; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.03.0290.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0290a; 4x5
- Two men in suits shaking hands at the head of the banquet table, hosted by Gulf.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0291; 4x5
- A man presenting another man with a plaque at the head of the table at a banquet hosted by the Gulf company. Plaque reads “To H.E. Estep in recognition and appreciation of our business association which began in 1929.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0292; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0293; 4x5
  Series 8c, “Other Events and Entertainment: Weddings,” begins.
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0294; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0295; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0296; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0297; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0298; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0299; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0300; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0301; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0302; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Getz-Sigler Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0303; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0304; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0305; 2.5x3.5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0306; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0307; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0308; 4x5
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0309; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0309a.
- Duplicate of P0002.03.0960.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0309a; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0309.
- Bride of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0310; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0311.
- Bride of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0311; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0310.
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0312; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0313.
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0313; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0312.
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0314; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0315.
- Bride and groom of the Tody-Branner Wedding.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0315; 3.5x5
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1. Housed with 0314.
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair, with a ferris wheel in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0316; 4x5
  Series 8d, “Other Events and Entertainment: Shenandoah County Fair,” begins. (See Series 7e and 11d).
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair, with a ferris wheel in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0317; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair, with banners advertising the “Alters Brothers United Assembly of the World’s Strangest People.” c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0318; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair, watching a man on stage with enlarged ribs.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0319; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fair, close-up view of a man who is severely sucking in his stomach.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0320; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fair, a woman and a man playing a game.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0321; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair walking between food vendors and games.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0322; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair standing and sitting in risers, watching a show or sporting event that is not pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0323; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair standing and sitting in risers, watching a show or sporting event that is not pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0324; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair viewing the merchandise of a glassware vendor.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0325; 4x5
- Crowds of people at the Shenandoah County Fair watching over the fence as an elderly man walks towards what seems to be a very old automobile.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0326; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fair, view of the 4-H Club display/booth. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0327; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fair, closer view of the 4-H Club display/booth, revealing it to be out of Saumsville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0328; 4x5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0329; 2.5x3.5
  Series 8e, “Other Events and Entertainment: Miscellaneous Entertainment,” begins.
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0330; 2.5x3.5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0331; 2.5x3.5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0332; 2.5x3.5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0333; 2.5x3.5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0334; 2.5x3.5
- A male acrobat, possibly under the roof of a large tent or outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0335; 2.5x3.5
- A large dog balancing/running on a barrel, making it roll.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0336; 2.5x3.5
- A woman dancing or doing a trick with a dog; a small orchestra or band is in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0337; 2.5x3.5
- A dog climbing up and down a free standing ladder, which a woman is holding for balance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0338; 2.5x3.5
- A dog balancing on a tight ropewalk, with a woman standing close by for support.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0339; 2.5x3.5
- A young woman playing a violin inside of a large cavern.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0340; 2.5x3.5
- A young woman playing a violin inside of a large cavern.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.03.0341; 2.5x3.5
- An automobile stuck in a large ditch with a small shed or other structure. VA License plate 64-512.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.04.0001; 2.5x3.5
  Series 9a, “Accidents and Disasters: Automobile Accidents,” begins.
- An automobile stuck in a large ditch with a small shed or other structure. VA License plate 64-512.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.04.0002; 2.5x3.5
- A severely damaged automobile hitched to a tow truck or other vehicle, VA License plate 566-521.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0003; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of a severely damaged automobile that is hooked up to a tow truck, VA license plate 566-521.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0004; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a severely damaged automobile that is hooked up to a tow truck, VA license plate 566-521.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0005; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0006; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0007; 2.5x3.5
- Very close-up view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0008; 2.5x3.5
- Inside view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0009; 2.5x3.5
- Very close-up view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0010; 2.5x3.5
- Very close-up view of a severely damaged vehicle.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0011; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of a wrecked automobile, VA license plate 412-037.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0012; 2.5x3.5
- Diagonal view of a wrecked automobile, VA license plate 412-037.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0013; 2.5x2.5
- Front view of a wrecked automobile, VA license plate 412-037.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0014; 2.5x2.5
- Front view of a vehicle that was forced into a large wooden pole, VA license plate 448-855.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0015; 2.5x3.5
- A vehicle that was forced into a large wooden pole, VA license plate 448-855.c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0016; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of a vehicle that was forced into a large wooden pole, VA license plate 448-855. c. 1947-1949, Image: P0002.04.0017; 2.5x3.5
- View of an automobile with a damaged front end, VA license plate 221-062.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.04.0018; 2.5x3.5
- View of an automobile with a severely damaged front end, VA license plate 221-062.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0019; 2.5x3.5
- View of an automobile with a severely damaged front end, VA license plate 221-062.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0020; 2.5x3.5
- Side view of an automobile with a severely damaged front end, VA license plate 221-062.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0021; 2.5x3.5
- A damaged vehicle stuck in a ditch, VA license plate 57-919.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0022; 2.5x3.5
- A crowd of people standing around an automobile accident.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0023; 2.5x3.5
- A crowd of people standing around an automobile accident.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0024; 2.5x3.5
- A crowd of people standing around an automobile accident.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0025; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of an automobile laying on its side at the edge of a road.c. 1948-1950, Image: P0002.04.0026; 4x5
- View from across the street of an automobile laying on its side. c. 1948-1950, Image: P0002.04.0027; 4x5
- An automobile laying on its side, with the top of the car pictured.c. 1948-1950, Image: P0002.04.0028; 4x5
- An automobile laying on its side, view from the front end of the car.c. 1948-1950, Image: P0002.04.0029; 4x5
- An automobile laying on its side, with the top of the vehicle pictured.c. 1948-1950, Image: P0002.04.0030; 4x5
- Side view of a car with a badly damaged front end.c. 1959-1961, Image: P0002.04.0031; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0032.
- Front view of a car with a badly damaged front end.c. 1959-1961, Image: P0002.04.0032; 2.5x2.5
- Accident involving a tractor-trailer and a pick-up truck, in front of The Valley Shop.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0033; 2.5x2.5
- Accident involving a tractor-trailer and a pick-up truck, in front of The Valley Shop. Same accident as in P0002.04.0033.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0034; 2.5x2.5
- Rear view of same accident as seen in P0002.04.0033-34.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0035; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0036.
- Alternate rear view of same accident as seen in P0002.04.0033-5.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0036; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0035.
- Rear view of a tractor-trailer accident on a street of a small town. Possibly same as in P0002.04.0036.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.04.0037; 2.5x2.5
- Front-end view of an automobile that is laying on its side on a residential street. A tractor-trailer is in the background. Possibly same as P0002.04.0037.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.04.0038; 2.5x2.5
- A number of men standing next to an automobile that is laying on its side; the wheels of a tractor trailer are pictured in the foreground. Possibly same as P0002.04.0038.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.04.0039; 2.5x2.5
- Front-end view of a vehicle that is laying on it side on a residential street. A tractor-trailer is in the background. Possibly same as in P0002.04.0039.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.04.0040; 2.5x2.5
- View of a tractor-trailer that has been in an accident in front of The Valley Shop. Possibly same as in P0002.04.0033-39.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0041; 2.5x2.5
- Front view of a tractor-trailer that has been in an accident. Presumably the same as in P0002.04.0041.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0042; 2.5x2.5
- Front view of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0033-42.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0043; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0044.
- Alternate front view of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0033-43.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.04.0044; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0043.
- Rear view of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0033-44, with skid marks pictured on the street.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.04.0045; 2.5x2.5
- View of a tractor-trailer that has suffered a bad accident, VA license plate 151-49.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.04.0046; 2.5x3.5
- Distant view of the same tractor-trailer as in P0002.04.0046.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.04.0047; 2.5x3.5
- Tractor-trailer after a serious accident, mangled in a ditch off the side of the road.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0048; 2.5x3.5
- Alternate view of the tractor-trailer accident as seen in P0002.04.0048.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0049; 2.5x3.5
- Alternate view of the tractor-trailer accident as seen in P0002.04.0048-49.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0050; 2.5x3.5
- A tractor-trailer laying on its side in a field of snow, not far from the road.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0051; 4x5
- Rear view of the tractor-trailer as seen in P0002.04.0051.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0052; 4x5
- Distant view of the tractor-trailer as seen in P0002.04.0051-2, pictured on the far left.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0053; 4x5
- A multi-tractor-trailer accident on a rural road; trucks from Associate Transport and H.P. Welch Co. included.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0054; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0055.
- Distant view of same accident as seen in P0002.04.0054.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0055; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0054.
- Same accident as in P0002.04.0054-5, but with a close-up view of the Associate Transport truck.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0056; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0057.
- Same accident as in P0002.04.0054-6.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0057; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0056.
- A large number of men walking through and examining the tractor-trailer accident as seen in P0002.04.0054-57.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0058; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0059.
- A group of men walking through and examining the tractor-trailer accident as seen in P0002.04.0054-58.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0059; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0058.
- Same accident as in P0002.04.0054-58, but with a close-up view of the H.P. Welch Co. truck.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0060; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0061.
- Same accident as in P0002.04.0054-60, but with a close-up view of the H.P. Welch Co. truck.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0061; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0060.
- A distant view of the accident and crowds as seen in P0002.04.0054-61.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0062; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0063.
- Same accident as in P0002.04.0054-62, but with a close-up of the H.P. Welch Co. truck.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0063; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0062.
- A tractor-trailer accident in a field near a rural road.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0064; 4x5
- View from the street of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0064, with a road sign identifying the road as Route 11.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0065; 4x5
- Close-up view of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0064-5.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.04.0066; 4x5
- Either a truck or trailer stuck in a ditch and severely damaged.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0067; 4x5
- Close-up view of the truck or trailer as seen in P0002.04.0067.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0068; 4x5
- Close-up view of the truck or trailer as seen in P0002.04.0067-68.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0069; 4x5
- Alternate close-up view of the accident as seen in P0002.04.0067-69.c. 1949-1951, Image: P0002.04.0070; 4x5
- The front-end of a severely damaged car that is sitting inside of a garage or auto shop. c. 1950-1959, Image: P0002.04.0071; 2.5x3.5
- Crowds of people standing near a vehicle that is badly damaged and sitting horizontally across a street.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0072; 2.5x3.5
- An automobile with a badly damaged front-end, and its passenger side door open. Same as in P0002.04.0072.c. 1940-1942, Image: P0002.04.0073; 2.5x3.5